片名：《宇宙天魔》
格林威治时间8月9日，下午2:30
August 9th, 2:30 PM,
Greenwich Mean Time.
H.M.S. 邱吉尔号的外太空
The HMS Churchill outward bound.
在英美空间站的一个节点上
On board a joint British/American
space team.
这次任务是研究哈雷慧星的运行轨道
Their mission:
to intercept and study
the comet bearing
Dr. Edmond Halley's name.
邱吉尔号是第一艘装备“那维”引擎的太空船
The Churchill is the first spacecraft
equipped with the Nerva engine.
邱吉尔号由推进器加速
It propels the Churchill
with constant acceleration,
在飞行器上第一次产生了
足够的类似地球的引力
enough to create Earth-type gravity
for the first time
on an extended flight.
这次考察是邱吉尔号的一次学习机会
The Churchill is on course
for its rendezvous.
- 长官，这是奇数
- 什么？
Sir, this is odd.
我得到一个跨越区段的雷达信号
What?
I'm getting a very small
radar cross section,
在沉睡的慧星核心之前
just ahead of the nucleus
in the coma of the comet.
我也得到了它，检查波长，
它在扫描仪边界按某一角度转动
I've got it too.
Check the length, Brendan,
it's at the limit of my angle of scan.
- 什么？在转动？
- 启动另一个设备检查
- What's going on?
- Did you chaps run an equipment check?
每五分钟转一次
I've been checking
every five minutes, sir.
- 速度150英里
- 150英里什么？
Radar state's 150 miles.
- 长度
- 150英里长？
- 150 miles what?
- Length.
Hundred and fifty miles long?
什么有150英里长？
What's 150 miles long?
是雷达追踪到的
It's a radar trace.
- 有东西在沉睡的慧星前
- 给我看看
Something right ahead
in the coma of the comet.
- E.G.R. 被确认
- 看起来很好
Show me.
EGR's confirmed.
E.G.R. 是最佳的
Looks good.
继续跟踪
EGR's optimal,
track three on three.
罗杰
Roget.
它的高度是多少？
What's the height of the thing?
高度至少有2里
I've got a vertical reading
of two miles, at least.
周围温度：6华氏度
Ambient temperature six degrees.
锰，钛含量少于百分之二
Iron less than 2%,
traces of manganese, titanium--
把基数调高试试
Try and raise base.
告诉他们那里隐藏着一个人造物
Tell them we have an artificial object
out here hidden in the--
- 你确定是想说“隐藏的”？
- 在慧星之上
Are you sure you want
to say hidden?
Tell them it's located
in the head of the comet.
保持监控，直到确认
Keep sending that
until they acknowledge.
使用下面的保护连接
Use a secured downlink.
对不起，指挥官，在狂风中许多东西都看不清
Sorry, Commander, everything's
being swamped by the coma winds.
我们不能把任何物体作为参照
We can't get anything
back to base.
灯火管制有多久？
How long's the blackout period?
任何时候
All the way.
你要做什么？
What are you gonna do?
继续
We're going in.
我们要去争取机会，戴尔维次
We're only gonna get
one chance, Derebridge.
那个东西在以后76年内是不会回来了
That thing won't be back
for another 76 years.
那时我们都死了
And we'll both be dead.
所以我们不得不弄清楚
We have to take a look now.
- 把“那维”发动机…
- 关了
Shut down Nerva.
关闭
Shutting down.
Down one.
Deltas plus one In two seconds.
- 收回太阳能板
- 检查，给我一个读数，鲍伯
- Solar panels retracted.
- Check.
Give me a readout, Bob.
运行E.V.A. 演习
你希望它是从哪里来的？
Where do you suppose
this thing came from?
- 它在考察慧星吗？
- 继续，让我们了解它
Was it exploring the comet,
do you think?
它表面看起来有许多伤痕
Surface looks badly pitted.
这说明它在这里有很长时间了
In that case,
it's been here a long time.
遗弃物？或者是什么
It's derelict, whatever it is.
邱吉尔号，到一边去，我们正在过来
罗杰、卡尔森，我们知道了，准备进来
Roger, Carlsen, we copy.
We have you going in.
邱吉尔号，它看起来像一些巨大的、有机的动脉
Churchill, looks like
some sort of giant artery-- organic.
我觉得它以前一直在这里
I almost have the feeling
I've been here before.
哦，小伙子
Oh, boy.
真是难以置信
我希望你能感谢雷达上的影像
I hope you can appreciate
the scale of this on the video.
罗杰，我们抓住它了，都在带子上
Roger, we're getting it.
It's all on tape.
哦，他妈的
Oh, shit.
哇，它在那里
Well, here they are.
邱吉尔号
它看起来像我们发现的飞船的拥有者
Churchill, it looks like we found
the occupants of the ship.
它们看起来像蝙蝠，巨大的蝙蝠
They look like bats...giant bats.
- 一定有数以百计
- 是数以千计
Churchill, there must be
hundreds of them.
Thousands...dead. I hope.
我希望是死的
看起来像史前的
已经完全干燥了
It's completely desiccated.
- 弄得碎？
- 是的，应该可以
- Crumbled.
- Yes.
It would.
隔了这么多年，应该干了
All the fluid's been lost to space
over the years.
我会装一点放进袋子里带回去
We'll bag this one,
take it with us.
我们正在将样品装入袋中
We're deploying
the specimen bag.
看起来像某种正在伸展的巨大结构
it looks like some sort
of big structure
that's just unfolding--
it's enormous!
好大
天啊，是什么？
God, what is it?
我们快离开这里，长官
Better get out of here, sir.
谁也不可以离开，留在那里
Nobody's goin' anywhere,
stay where you are.
邱吉尔号，我是卡尔森，那边发生什么事？
Churchill, this is Carlsen.
那东西已经停止了
What's happening out there?
The thing stopped opening.
唯一可以描述它的是：像一支巨大的伞
The only way to describe it is--
it's-- it's like a giant umbrella.
- 上帝啊，大得无法形容
- 邱吉尔号
Good god, it's--
it's absolutely enormous.
它正在做什么？
Churchill, what's it doing now?
没做什么，长官
Nothing, sir.
它已停止扩展了
It stopped opening.
它就停在那里
It's just sitting there.
- 能告诉我它的成分吗？
- 不是金属的
Tell what it's made of?
Not metal.
雷达波可以透过
It's radar transparent.
好
如果它又开始展开，告诉我…
Okay...if it starts up again,
let me know.
它的任何活动，知道吗？
Any activity out there,
you understand?
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
我们要去哪里？
That's where we're goin'.
这里有些东西
Something there.
指挥官，我是邱吉尔号
Commander,
this is Churchill.
我们正在失去信号，
我们已经遗失V.T.R.
We're losing our signal.
We've lost VTR.
进来，指挥官！
Come in, Commander.
三具尸体
Bodies, three bodies.
保护好
Perfectly preserved.
他们看着我是像看着一个…
They look to me to be like in--
像我身上发生了什么变化
Something's happening to me.
我怎么了？
What's wrong...
with me, wha--
what's wrong?
指挥官
Commander, come in.
我是邱吉尔号，你听到了吗？
This is Churchill.
Do you copy?
他们看起来像某类假死，或是睡着了
They seem to be in some sort
of suspended animation or sleep.
稍等，我们正在下来
Hold on, we're coming down.
邱吉尔号，如果你看…
Churchill,
Churchill, if you read,
这里有两男一女，都是裸体的
there are two nude males
and one female.
这是邱吉尔号，我们没有照像机，汤姆
This is Churchill,
we have no picture.
Come in, Tom.
邱吉尔号，我说我们发现了一个年轻女孩
Churchill...l said we found
a young girl.
“女孩”？ 你是指人类？
Girl?
You mean human?
完美的人类
Definitely humanoid.
我说她是完美的
I'd say she's perfect.
我在空间站六个月了，
对我来说，她看起来十分完美
I've been in space for six months
and she looks perfect to me.
- 戴尔维次，怎么回事？
- 怎么回事？
Derebrldge, what's wrong?
What's wrong...
你想要收回多少？我说收回三分之…
How many
do you want to take back?
I say we take back all three.
死的在另一间房中
One of the dead things
in the other chamber.
看看我们是否能够恢复他们
Well...
let's so.
If we can break 'om fr“.
（三十天后）
邱吉尔号，进来，这是英国任务控制中心
Churchill, come in,
this is Mission Control Great Britain.
你听到了吗？
Do you copy?
Come in, Churchill.
如果我们是来接他们的，
他们应该离我们近点
If they're going to pick us up,
they should get us this close.
没有收到信号，柯斯基博士
Simply aren't receiving,
Dr. Bukovsky.
飞船没有反应
Automatic circuits
don't even respond.
他们的无线电静默
They're radio dead.
上帝，我希望和他们通话
Christ.
I hope it's just
their communications.
...do you copy?
Come in, Churchill.
Churchill, come in,
this is Mission Control Great Britain.
Do you copy?
Come in, Churchill.
他们的轨道正常吗？
How's their orbit look?
就要停靠了，但还差一点点
You can see it's stable,
but they're slightly off.
他们应该要调整一下
但是他们没有
They should have adjusted coming in,
but they haven't.
你在那做什么？
What do you make of that?
我希望重新设定他们的路线
It would appear
that they, uh, set their course
在离开慧星后，到现在还没有更新
just after they left the comet.
I'd say it hasn't been
updated since.
- 哥伦比亚号？
- 哥伦比亚号
The Columbia?
升空，我们正在升空
The Columbia.
Lift of, we have lift off.
安全，控制塔
控制中心，这是哥伦比亚号
Control, this is Columbia.
我们被清除入坞程序？
Are we clear
to initiate docking procedure?
往前飞，哥伦比亚号，你们飞行正常
Go ahead, Columbia,
you are looking good.
停在软垫旁
Stand by for soft dock.
软垫
Soft dock.
软垫确认
Soft dock confirmed.
哥伦比亚号，船完好无损
Columbia,
the ship's completely gutted.
哦，上帝
Oh, my God.
休斯顿，有个问题，这里曾起过火
Houston, we have a problem.
There's been a fire.
我会看看
你们二个，试试顶上的甲板
I'll take a look in the tug bay.
You two try the top deck.
哥伦比亚号，他们都死了
Columbia, they're all dead.
哥伦比亚号，这里没什么，我准备进牵引坞
Nothing down here, Columbia.
I'm going on in to the tug bay.
我在拿磁带
I'll get the tapes.
- 我看到了
- 怎么除掉她的外壳？
I see-- how did you open
the girl's case?
我们不知道怎么开
We didn't, Minister.
我们正在讨论如何脱下外壳
We were just talking
about how to get it open
when it popped open
of its own accord.
- 你们将外壳照X光吗？
- 我们不确定是水晶做的
Did you x-ray the crystal cases?
We're not certain they're crystal.
外壳不是金属的，也不太像有机的
The casings are not metallic.
I'm not even sure they're organic.
外壳在那里，之前不是在那里
The casing is right there
in front of us without being there,
- 如果是真的…
- 那么人呢？
if that makes any sense.
And the bodies from the cases?
我们正准备解剖一个
We're going to do
our first dissection now.
当然可以，如果法拉达博士认为他们已死了
Provided, of course,
that Dr. Fallada agrees they're dead.
FaHada.
我不知道我是否有权力确定他们的死因
I don't know that I'm qualified
to pass judgment on alien death.
他们的存活机会难道比我们低吗？
You would agree
that they're less alive than we are?
昨天，香港黄金价格跌至谷底
Yesterday
in Hong Kong, gold closed lower.
欧洲的期货市场交易清淡…
In light trading
on European currency markets,
英磅对美元、马克的比价接近
the pound closed mixed
against the dollar
and West German mark
在稍后的新闻里，将公布市场报告
There will be a full market report
after the late news.
詹士葛兰姆从欧洲采访
This is James Graham reporting
from the city.
现在回到主播室
Now back to the newsroom.
...developments as they arise.
哈雷慧星从天空北部横过
Halley's Comet is now dominating
the northern skies,
在太空中延伸超过一亿公里
stretching over a hundred million miles
across the heavens,
在这格外地清静的夜晚…
occupying one-sixth
of the entire visible horizon.
地平线上六分之一的地方都可以看见
On this exceptionally clear night,
一群爱好者正在纪念
爱德蒙哈雷博士的重大发现…
a group of enthusiasts are
commemorating
Dr. Edmond Halley's great prediction
by holding an outdoor watching
在格林威治天文台创始时，
博士由手持望远镜观察到的
from the site of his original
observatory at Greenwich.
我们的观众可能对此感兴趣
Our viewers may be interested
to know that comets
慧星曾被认为是非常邪恶的
were once considered
to be harbingers of evil,
慧星最早的名字之一叫“灾祸”
and that one of the earliest words
for comet was disaster,
在拉丁文中的意思是“邪恶的星星”
which in Latin means evil star.
对深入宇宙考察的邱吉尔号来说
可能确实是邪恶的
And it may indeed be an evil star
for the deep space probe, Churchill.
尤其是在不能正确解释命运的王权时期
There's still no word
from Her Majesty's Government
不论他们是活还是死
as to the fate of the crew,
whether they're alive or dead.
我们只有等待进一步的研究
We can only await
further developments.
用我的身体
Use my body.
Bukovsky.
- 那个女郎在哪里？
- 她不见了
Bukovsky, where--
where's the girl!
She's gone.
我看见她了
I saw her.
这是她干的
She did that.
保安，法拉达教授在这里
Security.
Hello, Professor Fallada here.
我以柯斯基博士的名义命令
I'm calling at Dr. Bukovsky's orders.
- 把船长安全守册给我
- 是的，先生
Get me the Duty Security Captain now.
Yes, sir.
94号，控制中心，
你不会相信我看见了什么
Four nine to Control.
You'll never believe
what I'm looking at.
- 控制中心，你能再说一次吗？
- 我相信你听得到
Control, can you say that again?
I believe you heard me.
那个女孩在飞船中不见了，但绝对没有离开
There's a girl on the loose
in the building.
She must not leave.
对不起，我认为你说她是裸体的
Pardon me, but I thought you said
she was naked.
是的，我是那么说的，当然，你能找她
That's right, that's what I said.
一定是笑话
Surely, you can find her.
Must be some kinda joke.
真不敢相信
I don't believe it.
姑娘，你要去哪里？
All right, Miss,
just stay where you are.
你听说了吗？他们说已抓住她
You heard 'em,
they said grab her.
放松点，伙伴，她应该是好人
Take it easy, Link,
she's not in her right mind.
控制中心，我们已在主厅里找到那个女孩
Control, Control, we have located
the girl in the main lobby.
就是她，快来
That's it, come on.
- 喂
- 我们已经找到那个女孩，先生
Yes.
We've located the girl, sir.
- 在哪？
- 她在楼下的主厅里
- Whore?
- She's downstairs In the main lobby.
好的
Right.
- 她在主厅里，你快下去
- 不
She's in the main lobby.
- You all right to go down there?
- No.
好的
Come on, nice and easy.
快点，过来
Come on.
Come to me.
到爸爸这里来
Come to daddy, come on.
让她住手
Make it stop, make it stop!
快点！我们抓住她！
Come on, let's get her.
- 还好吧，伙计？
- 还好
- You all right, mate?
- Yeah.
把非军事区的人都清走
Will all non-involved
personnel please clear the area.
重复：每个与此无关的人…
I repeat-- Will everybody who has no
business to be here,
请马上离开，到安全的地方去
please clear the area
for your own safety.
这是警察警告
This is a police announcement.
Please keep right back--
对不起，先生，不准照相，请…
- Sony. gonthmon. no photos phat.
- Hun
好
Sorry.
- 你们当中哪一个是柯斯基博士？
- 是我
May I ask which of you
is Dr. Bukovsky?
我是来自S.A.S.的肯上校
lam.
I'm Colonel Caine.
刚才的警告不是对大家的，
那只是一个D级警告
From the S.A.S.?
Gentlemen, that last remark
is not for publication.
This is a D Notice situation.
不要靠太近
Not too close.
这是凶杀案，你说呢？
And this was murder...
you say?
再说一遍，你是怎么被那个女孩制服的？
Tell me again how the girl
overpowered you.
她…
She, uh...
那是我从没见过的，最不可思议的女人
was the most overwhelmingly
effeminate presence
I've ever encountered.
- 我们没有那个本事
- 它是女的吗？
I was drawn to her
on a level that--
是的，不可思议
Was it sexual?
Yes, overwhelmingly so.
非常可怕
告诉控制中心，尽量降低损失
And horrible.
当你进来的时候卫兵就死了吗？
Loss of control.
And the man, the guard, was dead
when you came into the room?
- 当他在的時候，你看到他？
- 是的
You found him as he is now?
Yeah.
女孩来自邱吉尔号飞船？
And the girl, she came
from the ship, Churchill?
嗯
Uh-huh.
她跟你说过话，用英语？
She spoke to you?
In English?
是的
That's right.
她怎么会讲英语？
How would she know English?
回去就说飞船的磁带在火灾中损坏了
Now, going back--
you say the ship's tapes
were destroyed in the fire?
没有被损坏
No, they weren't destroyed
in the fire.
那我们怎么告诉人们他们的死因？
That's what we were told
to tell the public.
被“杀死”？
They were erased.
同时，飞船的逃生舱不见了
Erased?
Also, the Churchill's escape pod
is missing.
- 有人生还了吗？
- 我们不知道
What's that mean,
did someone escape?
他这样的身体状况，很不幸…
They don't know.
Unfortunately,
the condition of the bodies
不可能问到有用的东西
make an accurate count impossible.
火焰的压力能够发射逃生舱吗？
Could the heat from the fire
have launched the pod?
No, no, no.
怎么起火的？
What started the fire?
飞船的氧气系统被引燃了，好大的火
The ship's oxygen system ignited.
It was a terribly hot fire.
你说的这些情况没有涉及到人形物体
Yet, you say the three cases
containing the bodies were untouched.
- 是的
- 你们在哪里发现的？
- That's correct.
- Where were they found?
在牵引坞，放太空拖船的地方
In the bay where the space tug
was stored.
别的都烧焦了
Where everything else
was charred.
让人难以置信，不是吗？
Incredible.
Is it not?
你已使用我们的技术调查了吗？
Have you examined the cases?
Using every technique we have.
X光扫描的结果得到的是模糊图像
X-ray scans of the cases
yield only blurred images.
- 那意味着什么？
- 他们不是物理对象
What does that mean?
They're not precisely physical objects.
比较像一个力场
More like a sort of force field.
这是我们力所不能及的
We're a bit out of our depth here.
是的，我知道，真是令人难以置信
The whole thing is--
Yes, I know.
Incredible.
他们对警卫做了尸体解剖吗？
我想不会
Have they done an autopsy yet
on the guard?
No, I suppose not.
那其他二个怎么样了？
What about your two other bodies?
上校，能原谅我吗？
Colonel, may I be excused?
似乎比我想象中的更令人作呕
I seem to be feeling a little more
nauseous than I thought.
是的
Yes, of course.
法拉达博士，从门上我注意到，
这是生物化学区
I notice from your door, Dr. Fallada,
that your area is biochemistry.
但是我知道你真正感兴趣的是…
But I understand
your real interest is--
是的，是死亡，肯上校
Death, Colonel Caine, correct.
死亡学
Thanatology is the name for it.
为你死是个政治问题
Death for you, Colonel, is a
bureaucratic problem-- who did it?
谁？ 何时？为什么？
When and why did they do it?
- 我对吗？
- 为你？
A problem to be solved,
am I correct?
我被死亡弄得神昏颠倒
And for you?
Well, I'm fascinated
by death itself--
当我们死后，会发生什么事？
在我们死之后，会发生什么事？
What happens as we die,
when we die.
- 你是指死亡后的生活？
- 是的
What happens after we die?
You mean, life after death.
死后的生活？
Yes.
- Is there?
- What?
Life after death.
你真的想要知道吗？
Do you really want to know?
不
No.
回答你的问题，是的，我是这样想的
But to answer your question,
yes, I think there is.
如果我猜对了，生命力将一直被保存…
If I am correct,
the life force is conserved
而且，甚至所有的东西死亡之后
always and in all things,
even after death.
你认为会发生在今晚？
And you think that applies
to what's happened here tonight?
是的
Yes.
我想那个姑娘，人…
Yes, I do.
I think that girl, creature,
能量，生命力…
drained energy,
life force,
部份地来自柯斯基博士，其余的来自守卫
partially from Bukovsky
and totally from the guard.
- 就像一个吸血鬼？
- 可能只有那样形容
A vampire?
It could be described that way, yes.
在某种意义上，我们都是吸血鬼
I mean, in a sense,
we're all vampires.
我们从其它的生命形式汲取能量
We drain energy
from other life forms.
不同的是程度而已
The difference is one of degree.
那个姑娘不是人
That girl was no girl.
她是外星生物
She's totally alien to this planet
and our life form.
对我们的生命形式构成危险
And totally dangerous.
天啊，该死
Jesus.
- 你相信那些小子还活着吗？
- 我宁可不信
Do you believe those blokes are alive?
I'm not paid to believe nothing, am I?
我相信他们还活着
I believe they're alive.
不要让我看到血腥的场面
Don't look bloody dead to me.
我们有麻烦了，但还在控制之中
We've had some trouble,
but everything's under control.
你要想知道得更多就到这里来
I think you better
come down here.
- 好的，长官
- 非常好
Yes, sir...very good, sir.
不要再发生这些，不能再有危险
It would appear these two
are no longer dangerous.
他们并没有被完全解剖
Well, there's certainly no possibility
of doing a full autopsy on them.
我要检查一下卫兵
I would like to examine the guard.
他们已开始检验卫兵的尸体了吗？
Have they started the autopsy
on the guard yet?
我相信如此
I believe so, sir.
这是一个年轻人，死了约两小时
This is an autopsy on the body
of a young man,
dead approximately two hours.
- 你说他只有二十多岁？
- 是的
Did you say he was about 20?
Yes, that's correct.
将上校放下来！
Get the Colonel down here,
quickly!
God.
快把他放到隔离房里！
Put him in an isolation cell,
quickly!
Sergeant.
我没办法了，他可能会死
I had no idea
that it could be passed on.
你想说什么？
What do you suggest?
我建议把他放在另一个隔离房里
I would recommend that you place
this body in another cell.
二个小时前卫兵受到了攻击
It was two hours ago
that the guard was attacked.
如果还在这里看到下一个，我不会觉得惊讶
I won't be at all surprised
if we're seeing a pattern here.
- 在他说话的時候，做你的事，凯利
- 是的，升官
- Do as he says, Kelly.
- Yes, sir.
我在想被我们射中的那两个男的
Also, I want the two other bodies
that were shot-- the males.
收集这些碎片，检查一下
Collect the pieces and watch them.
- 打电话给英国内政大臣
- 好的
Get me the Home Secretary
on the line now.
Sir.
- 叫上校来
- 你已经叫了
Call for the Colonel, sir.
Sir, you have a call.
Caine.
Sir, we've found
a naked girl in Hyde park.
The body is
in an indescribable condition.
我马上就到
I'll be right there.
他们刚在海德公园发现了一个人，
一个裸体女人
They've just found a body
in Hyde Park.
他们说，她处在一种难以形容的状态下
A naked girl.
They say she's
in an indescribable condition.
那可能是你们遗失的女孩吗？
Could that be your girl?
- 哦？
- 那不是她
- Well?
- That's not her.
巡视员，那两个小伙怎么样？
Inspector, what about the two boys?
他们早就在公园里
Oh, yes, they were
in the park earlier, sir.
我想，我们可能更早就看到她了
Yeah, we saw her.
I think.
Earlier.
那看起来像她的头发
Any rate,
that looks like her hair.
No, that's why we notices her.
- 她和一个黑头发女子在一起
- 她们两个身上穿衣服吗？
She was with a dark haired girl.
她们真的好漂亮
Real good looking bird and all.
Didn't have a lot of clothes on either.
我们认为她们应该很好
We thought they might be--
well, you know.
哦，你看见黑头发姑娘到哪里去了？
Yes.
Well, did you see where they went,
where the dark haired girl went?
没有看到
No, no, we didn't.
我们在她们后面转圈，
也许我们可以看见…
We angled on back
to see if maybe we could--
看她们在做什么
you know,
see 'em doing something.
- 我们什么时候发现她
- 是多久以前的事？
- That's when we found her.
- How long ago was that?
- 半个小时前
- 他打电话给我们，然后我们打电话给你
Half an hour ago.
Yeah, this lad phoned us
and then we phoned you, sir.
谢谢你，巡视员
Yes, thank you, Inspector.
显然，这是那个姑娘干的
Obviously, the work of the girl.
我们可以将这具及另外的尸体送回控制中心吗？
You think we can have this body sent
back to the center with the others?
好，那是个好主意
Yes, I suppose that's a good idea.
巡视员，发现别的东西就告诉我
Inspector, let me know if you find
anything else, will you?
- 我们会将她带回去
- 好的，长官
We'll be taking her back with us.
Very good, sir.
现在她有衣服了
Now she has clothes.
我想你看到了什么
There's something
I want you to see, sir.
汉斯·法拉达博士，珀西·赫塞尔廷爵士
和内政大臣
Dr. Hans Fallada, Sir Percy Heseltine,
the Home Secretary.
你们来得正是时候
You're just in time.
正好是两个小时
It's exactly two hours.
Please help me.
这是那个被太空女郎制服的卫兵
This is the guard who was originally
overcome by the space girl.
Please.
开始转化时，我觉得好恐怖…
As I feared,
once transformed,
受害人必须注入能量…
the victims need
regular infusions of energy.
- 另外…
- 另外什么？
Otherwise--
Otherwise what?
哦，我的上帝，亲爱的上帝！
Oh, my God.
Dear God.
那个被卫兵攻击的病理学家
And down here we have the pathologist
who was attacked by the guard.
- 是吗？
- 他，也需要营养
- See.
- He too needs feeding.
我们在公园中看到的那个姑娘，
会发生相同的事情…
The same thing is going to happen
to that girl we found in the park.
大约一个小时
In about one hour.
天哪！
Have there been
any further reports, Kelly?
我们在这里公布情况时，
某人就立即来了
No, sir, we set up
to get the calls here
- 什么？
- 没什么
the instant one comes in.
- What?
- Nothing.
你说这些人是从邱吉尔号带回来的？
You say these creatures were brought
back from the Churchill?
是的，但不是这个，她也是受害者
Yes, sir, but not this one.
She's a victim of the creatures.
好，得到他们时邱吉尔号在哪里？
Yes, yes, but where did
the Churchill acquire them?
目前，我们无法确定
We have no way
of determining that at present.
- 也许都在发生变化
- 什么？
- Perhaps that's all changing.
- What?
我刚从美国帕萨迪纳州的J.P.L.收到一条消息
I've just received a call
from the JPL in Pasadena.
Seems the Goldstone tracking disc has
just picked up something
他们说邱吉尔号的逃生仓已返回地球
they think is Churchill's escape pod--
- 在哪个地方？
- 德克萨斯州
reentering the Earth's atmosphere.
Where?
Texas.
Come on, guys, hurry It up.
All right, take it easy now.
Hey, buddy, you all right?
哪里？瓦尔特雷德陆军医院？
Where?
Walter Reed Army Hospital?
他受伤了吗？好像很疲惫
Is he hurt?
该死，到那里去！
Just exhausted, you say.
Well, get him the hell over here!
- 卡尔森上校呢？
- 他在等你们
Colonel Carlsen,
they're expecting you, sir.
卡尔森上校
Colonel Carlsen, sir.
汤姆
Tom.
我认为你已经死了呢
I thought you were dead.
Bukovsky.
让我介绍一下，这位空军勤务处的肯上校
Colonel Carlsen,
allow me to introduce
Colonel Caine
of the Special Air Services.
You already know Dr. Fallada.
Colonel.
来，坐下
Take a seat, won't you?
我很抱歉在这种情况下叫你们来
I'm sorry to drag you
over here like this, Tom.
相信你们宁愿与漂亮的护士在一起
I'm sure you'd rather be recuperating
with a pretty nurse.
我们必须知道邱吉尔号上发生了什么
Tom, we've got to know
what happened on the Churchill.
嗯，当然
Yes, of course.
对你们来说，那可能非常困难…
我准备说，要接受…
It may be, uh...very difficult for you
to accept what I'm going to say.
相信你们要告诉我们所有的事，会有一点困难
We'll have very little difficulty
believing anything
you have to tell us, Colonel.
- 继续
- 你已知道什么？
Do go on.
在邱吉尔号上，起火了
You know something?
There was a fire
aboard the Churchill.
你可能对三个人型生物感兴趣…
You might be interested to know
不被大火烧毁
that the bodies of the three humanoids
were not destroyed in that fire.
让他们在火灾中幸免于难
They survived in their cases.
把他们带到伦敦，但女的已经逃脱
They were brought
down here to London,
and the female has escaped.
她已经杀三个人了
She's killed three people already.
哦，上帝
Oh, my God.
因为时间紧急，
所以无论如何，你必须告诉我们…
So you see, Colonel, whatever
you have to tell us is rather pressing.
告诉我们发生了什么
Please tell us what happened.
我们发现这些人形物体来自外太空的飞船
We found the bodies
aboard the alien spacecraft.
什么，外太空的飞船？
What alien spacecraft?
上校，一开始就这样猜的
Colonel, take it
from the beginning.
保守地说，假设我们对那些麻烦一无所知
Assume we know nothing.
Which is understating the matter.
我们在距哈雷慧星9000英里
内接近了哈雷慧星
We approached within 9,000 miles
of Halley's Comet,
在昏睡的慧星里发现了某个东西
when we detected an object
in the comet's coma.
我们发现这些人形物体后，
将他们带到了邱吉尔号上
After we discovered
the bodies,
we transferred them
to the Churchill.
我们找到三个像人的生物
还有一些像蝙蝠的东西
We have in tow,
the three humanoid creatures
and one of the bat-like things.
这是邱吉尔号，欢迎你们回来
This is Churchill, we copy.
Welcome back.
罗林斯，准备返回地球了吗？
You gotten through
to Earth yet, Rawlings?
不，长官，慧星尾部的的温度在升高
No, sir, and the tail
of the comet's heating up.
- 戴尔维次，为什么会那样？
- 我不知道，汤姆
What's the matter Derebridge?
I don't know, Tom.
我觉得在消耗能量
I feel drained.
你？
Do you?
我感到很鼓舞
你没事吧？
I feel invigorated.
You okay?
- 我很好
- 好
Yeah.
- I'm fine.
- Okay.
每个人都会回到空间站
Everybody back
to their stations.
把我们从这里受的罪赶走
Let's get the hell outta here.
在回地球的路上，队员开始死亡…
On the trip back to Earth,
the crew began to die--
一个接一个
one by one.
罗林斯…
无线电船员，第一个去世
Rawlings, the radio officer,
was the first to go.
罗林斯不承认他做了什么
Rawlings denied any knowledge
of what he had done.
我不记得
I don't remember.
罗林斯
Rawlings,
除我之外，在前一个小时，你是唯一没睡的
besides myself, you're the only one
that's been up here
in the last hour.
我最近觉得很虚弱…
I've been feeling weak recently.
不是我自己
Not myself.
真的记不起来
Just don't remember.
第二天，我们发现罗林斯的尸体
We found Rawlings' body
the next day.
如何是好？
他死了吗，上校？
Exactly how did he die, Colonel?
他只是耗尽了生命
The life just drained out of him.
一个接一个…
One by one...
其他的队员也开始死亡
the rest of the crew
began to die.
不知何故…
Somehow...
我不知道该怎么办…
I don't know how...
我幸存下来了
I held out.
我觉得将会有麻烦
It just seemed to be
a matter of will.
我一直在想…
I always thought...
那个姑娘…
The girl...
啊？ 女孩？
Yes, the girl?
我记不起了
I can't remember.
我记得下一个…
从控制室窗户往外看…
What I remember next is the view
out of the observation window--
在进入地球轨道前
coming in to Earth's orbit.
我不能让带回去的东西伤害到地球
I couldn't expose the world
to what we'd brought back with us.
于是我决定把他们全部毁掉
I was determined
to destroy them all.
这是我做过的最难做的决定
It was the hardest thing
I ever did.
能够理解
We understand.
下这个决心需要很大的勇气
Must have taken great courage
to try and make--
不，你不了解
No, you don't understand.
我的一部份不想离开
Part of me didn't wanna leave.
她杀了我所有的朋友，
而我仍然不想离开
She killed all my friends
and I still didn't want to leave.
离开她是我做过的最难做的事
Leaving her was
the hardest thing I ever did.
卡尔森上校看起来很疲惫
Colonel Carlsen
looks exhausted to me.
我们应该让他睡一会，稍后再继续
I think we should allow him
to get some sleep.
好
Continue with this later.
Very well.
谢谢你，上校
Thank you, Colonel.
美国航空航天局追踪我们和我们的…
NASA tracking and ours
才离开哈雷慧星，报告不同寻常的结构
have just reported and unusual
structure leaving Halley's Comet.
What is it?
目标的雷达扫描结果
Radar ranging reports
the object is a needle-like shape,
针状物体，150英里长
one hundred and fifty miles long.
它的运行路线对准了地球的轨道…
Its present course projects out
into a perfect Earth orbit
在一两天内
in a little more than two days.
我刚刚接到总理的电话
Oh, and I've just received a call
from the Prime Minister.
准备在唐宁街开一个会
There's going to be a meeting
at Downing Street.
总理想要知道答案
PM wants answers.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
你正在把你的生活给我
You're giving me your life.
你正拥有它
You're taking it.
我的生命力在外泄
You're draining me.
你拿我的太多了
You're taking too much of me.
只是一个梦
It was a dream.
- 做的什么梦？
- 那个姑娘，她来看我了
Just a dream.
What dream, Carlsen?
The girl, she visited me.
来看你？怎么啦？
Visited you,
visited you how?
在我的脑海里
In my mind.
她…她和我有某种类型的思想沟通
She...she...she...
she had some kind
of mental contact with me.
她正汲取我的精力
She's draining me.
将那个梦告诉我们
Tell us about the dream, Carlsen.
我记不清了
I can't, it's gone.
记不清了
It's faded.
你介意试一次吗？
Carlsen, have you ever
been hypnotized?
No.
Do you mind
if I have a go at it?
It may help you
with your dreams.
好，试一试
Yeah, let's try it.
- 现在不行，他太疲惫了
- 好的，那就在明早
Not now, he's too exhausted.
Fine, fine, in the morning.
盯着它，正到眼睛有点累，然后闭上眼睛
Just stare at it
until your eyes feel tired.
你感到非常疲累，好想睡觉
Then close them.
You'll feel very tired.
Very sleepy.
她似乎在梦中和我说话
She seems to...
speak to me in my dreams.
她…
She...
那个姑娘…
我觉得…
the girl, I feel...
你觉得她什么？
What do you feel
for her, Carlsen?
我觉得非常…
I feel very...
靠近她
close to her.
她在摸你吗？
Is she in touch with you?
我想是的
I feel...
好像我的灵魂…
as if my mind...
不完全是我自己的
is not entirely my own.
如果她接触到你的灵魂…
If she is in contact
with your mind, Carlsen,
也许你正在跟她接触
perhaps you are
in contact with hers.
你看见她吗？
Can you see her?
你能见到她在哪里吗？
Can you see where she is?
Where is she now, Carlsen?
一个地方，我不知道地名
A place, I don't know
the name of it.
她正在走路
She's walking.
有着一张不同的脸…
She has a different face.
但是确实是她
But it's her.
“一张不同的脸”？那是为什么？
A different face,
how can that be?
她在使用一个不同的身体
She's using a different body.
- 她在做什么？
- 在找一个男人
What is she doing?
She's looking for a man.
什么男人？
What man?
任何男人，一个健康的男人
Any man.
- 她想要杀他吗？
- 不
A healthy man.
Does she intend to kill him?
- 为什么不？
- 她害怕被抓住
- No.
- Why not?
She's afraid of being caught.
她怎会被抓住的？身体会出卖她
How could she be caught?
她想做什么？
The body'd give her away.
So, what Is she hoplng to do?
她想要…
She wants to...
从他那里汲取一些能量
draw some energy from him.
不是完全地杀死他
Not enough to kill him.
- 她能做得到？
- 是的
She can do that?
Yes.
还有个另外的想法
There's another mind.
是的
Yes...
姑娘的名字…
叫亚伦
the girl's name is Ellen.
有二个人在一个身体中？
You mean there are
two people in one body?
二个灵魂？
Two minds?
亚伦和吸血鬼？
Ellen and the vampire?
是的
Yes.
她正在看一个男人
She's watching a man.
那男的在做什么？
What is the man doing?
停下车，在做些什么
He's parked--
Doing something with his car.
车子牌照
License number.
你能看到车牌号码吗？
Can you see
the license number of his car?
看得到
Yes.
F-M-C
129E…
1-2-9-E.
或者R
Or, uh...R.
汽车是什么牌子的？
What is the make of the car?
白色的沃尔沃
A white Volvo.
她现在在干什么？
What is she doing now?
Does she ask him his name?
她在拉她的裙子…
She's...
pulling her skirt...
拉到膝盖上方
over her knees.
她是…
She's...
他是…
He's...
把他的…
putting his...
手放在大腿上
his...
hand...
on her le-- on her leg.
FMC129E或者可能是R
F-M-C-1-2-9-E or possibly R,
一辆白色的沃尔沃
belonging to a white Volvo.
汽车司机搭载了一个叫做亚伦的姑娘
The driver of the car picked up
a girl named Ellen.
我必须知道那个姑娘是谁
以及能在哪里找到她
I have to know who the girl is
and where we can find her.
她与上述情况有关
She's connected with the case.
车在路上开，我说不清了
谢谢
I can't explain
over an open line.
Thank you.
你认为他说了实话吗？
Do you think he's telling
the truth about the girl?
再见
Well, we'll soon see.
好厉害啊，她能从一个身体动到另一个身体
从一个灵魂到另一个灵魂…
How brilliant if she is moving
from body to body, mind to mind.
只要从每个受害者取得少部分能量
Taking only a small amount
of energy from each victim.
那会更有意思，我们不会再发现新的受害者
It would make sense
that we're finding no new victims.
如果她没有痕迹地离开
She's hoping
to leave no trail.
如果那个姑娘不是在她最初的身体里，
她的身体在哪里？
If the girl is no longer
in her original body,
where is her body?
- 藏起来了
- 那我们找找看
Hidden.
Let's find it.
假如这些猜测是对的
Supposing you're right
about all of this,
那艘船在那里干嘛？它正做什么？
what about that ship up there?
我们不知道，但是我们想像最坏的结果
What's it doing?
We can't know that.
But we've got
to assume the worst.
也许是传说中的吸血鬼
Maybe they're like
the vampires of legend.
怎么是那个？
How's that?
他们会用棺材运他们到地球来
They would carry
their earth with them--
他们不会？
in their coffins, wouldn't they?
- 我们有来自夏威夷的食物
- 它来这里了
We have
a three meter feed from Hawaii.
- 把它放在一号屏幕
- 从240000英里开始
Here it comes.
Put It on screen number one.
Coming in 240,000 miles.
我的天啊，好大
My God, it's immense.
休，你有皮纸吗？
I say, Hugh, do you have
that skin tissue sample I asked for?
好
Oh, good.
好的，我会一直跟踪
Yes, of course I'll follow
containment procedure.
And Hugh,
send in that soldier, please.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
法拉达博士
Dr. Fallada?
一会见，警官，谢谢
Just one moment, Sergeant.
Thank you for coming around.
不久又会见面的
I'll be with you shortly.
追踪那辆车是血腥的、糟糕的工作
Bloody awful job,
tracing that car.
他名叫奈德·埔莱，住在约克郡
It belongs to a man named Ned Price
who lives in Yorkshire.
- 我们已拘留他了
- 那个姑娘呢？
We have him
under detention now.
正如你所说，
他说他搭载的姑娘是个叫亚伦的护士
What about the girl?
The girl he picked up was
a nurse named Ellen.
As you said,
EIIen-something-or-other.
And he dropped her off
at Thurlstone Hospital
after spending
the afternoon with her.
他不愿意谈这些，那个男的很累
He was most reluctant
to talk about it.
The man's totally exhausted.
是不是在精神病收容所？
Thurlstone.
Isn't that an asylum
of some sort?
是的，为患精神病的罪犯准备的
Yes, for the criminally insane.
（芙尔斯通医院）
你好吗？我是阿姆斯壮医生，医院的院长
How do you do, Home Secretary,
I'm Dr. Armstrong,
director of the hospital.
到我办公室来谈
Come with me to my office.
- 一个寒冷的夜晚
- 好冷
What a cold night.
Bitterly cold.
这是护士的房子
This is the nurse's house.
埃伦·唐纳森住在五号
Ellen Donaldson is number five.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们要不要讨论一下，并介绍一下你？
Shouldn't I come up
and introduce you?
- 不要了
- 跟我来，阿姆斯壮医生
I'd rather you didn't.
我还有些事要与你谈谈
Come along, Dr. Armstrong,
you and I have several matters
to discuss.
Come along.
喂？你是谁？
Yes, who is it?
我叫科林·肯，阿姆斯壮医生带我来的
Miss Donaldson,
my name's Colin Caine.
我想和你谈谈，可以进来吗？
Dr. Armstrong brought me over.
Id' like to talk to you.
May I come in?
你好
Yes?
- 你要问什么？
- 我叫科林·肯
What do you want?
这是美国空军卡尔森上校
My name's Colin Caine.
This is Colonel Carlsen,
United States Air Force.
我们可以进来和你说话吗？
我们已经见过阿姆斯壮医生
May we come in
and talk to you?
We have seen Dr. Armstrong.
可以坐下吗？
May I sit down?
我想问一下，与你一起吃午饭的，
名叫奈德·埔莱男子的事
I want to ask you about the man
you spent the afternoon with,
Ned Price.
- 我不知道你在说什么
- 我想你知道
I don't know
what you're talking about.
- 让我看见你的手
- 对不起，你想…
I think you do.
Let me see your hand.
Beg your pardon?
你在那里，不是吗？
You're in there, aren't you?
- 我不知道你在说什么
- 告诉我
I don't know.
Tell me.
No!
Carlsen!
她已经从她这里离开了，
现在在另外一个人的身体中
It's gone from her,
it's in another body now.
你如何知道的？
我能够看到，在她的脑海里
How do you know that?
I can see it in her mind.
她正在反抗，我要强迫她告诉我
She's resisting.
I'm gonna have
to force her to tell me.
不论外表，这个婊子喜欢被虐待狂
Despite appearances,
this woman is a masochist.
一个极端的被虐待狂
An extreme masochist.
她想我用武力从她那里得到什么
She wants me
to force the name out of her.
她想要我伤害她
She wants me to hurt her.
我可以从她脑海里看见图像
你想留一会吗？
I can see the images
in her mind.
Do you want to stay?
我在外面等，我不是个窥淫狂
Otherwise, wait outside!
Not at all.
I am a natural voyeur.
你进去吗？
Are you in there?
你在那里吗？
Are you there?
去吧
Let go.
现在
Now!
I've got a physical description.
最好叫人去照料唐纳森护士
Doctor, you'd better send someone
to look after Nurse Donaldson.
If I described one of the inmates
to you, could you identify him?
可以
Possibly.
大块头、肥胖、白头发、脸上有胎记
Big man, fat, gray hair.
杰弗里·赛克斯，婴儿杀手
你是如何知道的？
Birthmark on his face.
Jeffrey Sykes,
the child murderer.
Where did you get
his description?
- 他现在在哪里？
- 在单独监禁房里
Where is he now?
He's in solitary confinement.
Look, what is this about?
- 我们可能在这里呆一段时间
- 最好呼叫伦敦
What we're looking for
has moved.
We could be here some time.
- 可以用你的电话吗，医生？
- 当然可以
I better call London.
- May I use your telephone, Doctor?
- Certainly.
- 我们现在必须看到赛克斯
- 不能一直等到早晨吗？
We have to see Sykes now.
Oh, couldn't this wait
until the morning?
好的，我安排下
Oh, all right, I'II arrange it.
你要对所有事负责，指挥官
Anything to oblige,
Commander.
我不希望如此神秘
I wish this were not
so mysterious.
如果与警察有关，我有权知道吗？
If the police are involved,
haven't I a right to know?
如果你要对我的病人胡闹…
I mean, if you're going to start
messing about my patient.
阿姆斯壮医生，我当然赞成你的立场
Dr. Armstrong, I sympathize
with your position, of course.
然而，我可以告诉你，这关系到国家安全
However, I can tell you it is a matter
of national security.
我知道
I see.
你认为不应该给我介绍…
But, don't you think
that I should be present in any case
试探我的耐心？
to represent the interests
of my patient.
- 你知道…
- 我可以与你单独谈谈吗？
- You 300--
- Can I talk to you for a second?
可以
Of course.
他只有四岁孩子的智商
Uh...the man has the IQ
of a child of four.
那意味着我应该顺从肯上校吗？
Well, that's a decision,
I'm afraid,
I shall have to defer
to Colonel Caine.
是的，当然是的，你可以在一起来
我们可以开始了吗？
Yes, of course
you can come along.
- 你要对他做什么？
- 我想对他施催眠术
Can we start now?
What are you going
to do to him?
I'd like to hypnotize him.
那是什么？
What's that?
喷妥撒（钠）和吗啡
Pentothal and morphine.
为管理病人、预备催眠状态用的
I'd recommend it for pre-hypnosis
and patient management.
嗯，他看起来很安静
Well, he seems quiet.
你准备好我们就开始，拉姆森
We're ready when you are.
长官
- Lamson.
- Sir.
打针会有危险吗？
Can the injection be dangerous?
他应该能够忍受
He should have
no difficulty tolerating it.
总要冒点险，长官
There's always a risk, sir.
我要打那个？
May I have that?
我准备叫醒他
Well, I'll wake him up.
- 你们在干什么？！
- 停下来
- What are you doing!
- Stay where you are.
他生病了，拉姆森，
帮帮我们，我现在无法解释
He's sick, Lamson, help us,
I can't explain now.
这里有凶手，珀西爵士
There's our killer, Sir Percy.
真是疯了
It's madness.
我想问他，可以在哪里找到她？
I want to question him
before it wears off.
在坡道上，长官
Where can we take him?
Up the ramp, sir.
我们要独处一会
We need to be alone
for a minute, Lamson.
你知道他怎么样了？
How the devil
did you know it was him?
在护士的住处，他用肩碰了我
In the nurses quarters
he touched me on the shoulder.
我在他的脑海看到的
I saw into his mind.
The Colonel appears to be able
to see in the minds
先生，在那女孩的身体旁，谁能够保持镇静
of people who have been possessed
by the girl creature, sir.
当我触碰他的时候，就发生了
把他抱到桌上
It happens when I touch 'em.
Let's get him on the table.
怎么样？
How?
你怎么知道她仍然在阿姆斯壮院长身体里？
How do you know
she's still inside Armstrong?
有什么可以阻止她移动到其他人？
What's to prevent her
from moving to someone else?
她被困住
She's trapped.
我能感觉到
I can feel that.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
不
No.
- 拉姆森
- 长官？
- Lamson.
- Sir?
- 给我一份麻醉剂
- 一份常量的麻醉剂，长官？
Can you bring me another dose
of the hypnotic drug?
I suppose so, sir.
- 这不同寻常
- 这东西可以持续多久？
One dose is usually enough.
This is not a usual situation.
- 一份剂量？
- 一份剂量一小时
How long does the stuff last?
A dose like that?
我们一定会需要更多
A couple of hours.
We'll definitely need more.
- 给我三份剂量
- 三份？！
Bring me three doses.
我会负责，你只要拿过来
- Three?
- I'll take responsibility, Lamson--
Sir Percy and myself,
just get on with it.
好的，长官
Yes, sir.
三份剂量是否安全？
Is a second dose safe?
确实会损害他的心脏
Surely it can strain his heart.
瞧，你不知道我们正在处理
Look...you don't know
what we're dealing with here.
如果她摆脱了会很危险，她会逃跑
If he slips out from under,
she'“ escape.
阿姆斯壮
你听到吗？
Armstrong, can you hear me?
阿姆斯壮，如果你听到，就说好
Armstrong, if you can hear me,
just say yes.
It...
如果不想我…
won't let me...
和你说话
ta-- talk to you.
阿姆斯壮，阿姆斯壮
Armstrong,
Armstrong!
如果你知道谁是控制你的人？
Can you see what it is
that's holding you prisoner?
知道，是她
Yes, yes, she--
告诉她，她必须和我说话！
Tell her she has
to talk to me!
Tell her!
进来
Yes?
我带来了喷妥撒（钠）
Pentothal,
I brought the pentothal.
谢谢，这是全部的
Thanks, Lamson, that'll be all.
No.
抓住他
Hold him.
这里不需要那些
There's no need for that.
No need.
你在那里吗？你还能听到吗？
You in there,
can you still hear me?
你能进入他的脑海，她的脑海？
Can you get into his mind?
Her mind?
不要用这种麻药，它像一面墙
Not with this drug,
it's like a wall.
也许打多了
Perhaps you've given him
too much.
住嘴
- Perhaps we--
- Shut up!
听着，臭婊子
Listen, you bitch,
如果我需要，我会把你留在这个几个星期
I'll keep you in this state
for weeks, if I have to.
现在，你和我说话
Now, you talk to me.
卡尔森，和我在一起
Carlsen, be with me.
- 你想从我这里要什么？
- 我爱你
What do you want from me?
I love you.
你是什么？
What are you?
你为什么如此像人类，如此完美？
Why are you so human?
So perfect?
什么飞船上的鸟人？
What are the bird creatures
on the ship?
我们的身体并不重要
Our bodies are unimportant.
当你们这些男人在飞船上靠近…
As you and your men
have approached in your ship,
我为你换了他们
we changed them.
For you.
我们进入了你的脑海…
We entered your minds
并发现了那些新身体
and found there new bodies.
我替换了你们的思想
I took my shape
from your mind.
我使用了你们的语言
I took your language.
我变成了女人，直到在那里被发现…
I became the woman
I found there,
在你思想最深处，你最需要的
in your deepest thoughts,
your deepest needs.
我是你想像中的女人，卡尔森
I am the feminine
in your mind, Carlsen.
Where are you?
你在哪里？
Where are you!
你的身体在哪里？
Where's your body!
让我去找！让我去找！
Let me go!
- 卡尔森，摸我一下
- 你在哪？
Touch me, Carlsen.
Let me go.
Let me go!
- 已经正在传播
- 怎么啦？
- It's already spraadlng.
- How?
你无法阻止了，太晚了
You didn't stop it,
it's too late.
我们跟了她一半
That's impossible, we've been only
half a step behind her all the way.
这位先生已经停止呼吸
Sir, this gentleman's
stopped breathing.
也没有脉膊
There's no pulse either.
我想他的脖子断了
Sir, I think his neck is broken.
为珀西爵士准备一个担架，
为阿姆斯壮博士也准备一个
Lampson, prepare two stretchers.
One for Sir Percy
and one for Dr. Armstrong.
为旅行准备好药物
Prepare all your remaining doses
of the drug for travel.
好的，长官
Yes, sir.
你说无法阻止，它仍在传播
You said the thing
hadn't stopped,
it was still spreading.
- 你为什么那样说？
- 不知道
Why did you say that?
她可能是故意引着我们离开伦敦？
I don't know.
Could the girl have been deliberately
leading us away from London?
我们找得到全部受害者吗？
Is it possible we didn't find
all of her victims?
除公园那个，如果有其他的…
If we didn't find all
the victims,
if there are others
besides the girl in the park.
- 那就会传播
- 产生连锁反应…
The thing would spread.
几何学上，到如今为止…
And a chain reaction,
geometrically, until by now...
天哪
Oh, Christ.
中尉，可以用无线电呼叫伦敦的S.R.C.吗？
Lieutenant, can we use the radio
to get through to the S.R.C. in London?
稍等片刻，长官，可以呼叫的
Just a moment, sir,
there's something coming through.
是S.R.C. ，给你和卡尔森的
It is the S.R.C., sir,
for you and Carlsen.
Caine, can you hear me?
法拉达，大声点！我听不到！
Fallada, speak up,
I can't hear you.
那两个男的没死
The two males didn't die.
他们进入了士兵身体…
They jumped to the bodies
of the two soldiers who shot them
而且把两个士兵的身体变成了自己的
and transformed the soldiers bodies
into their own likenesses.
与他们和他们的受害者不同的是
That's the difference between them
and their victims.
受害人的灵魂不能离开他们的身体，
只有最初的三个能够做到
The victims can't leave
their bodies.
Only the original three
can do that.
- 我已杀了他们其中的一个
- 什么其中一个？
But I've killed one of them.
两个男吸血鬼中的一个
- One of which?
- One of the two male vampires.
- 正在变换的一个
- 怎么杀死的？
One of the transformed ones.
How did you kill him,
Fallada, how?
卡尔森，老办法
The old way, Carlsen.
一根含铅的金属棍，不是刺穿心脏…
A leaded metal shaft,
penetrating not through the heart,
而是在心脏下面两英寸，穿过他们的能量中心
but through the energy center
two inches below the heart.
不是钢，是铅铁混合物
Not steel, but leaded iron.
卡尔森，能行吗？
Right, Carlsen?
- 你还在那里吗？
- 是的
Are you there, Carlsen?
卡尔森，你和肯…
Yes.
Carlsen, you too, Caine,
我的信仰…
传说中的吸血鬼就像是这些人形生物
it is my belief
that the vampires of legend
came from creatures
such as these.
也许就是这些人型生物
Perhaps even
from these very creatures.
我知道有点让人难以置信
I know it sounds incredible.
你在听我说话吗？
Do you hear me, Carlsen!
比信仰更多是事实
It's morn than a ballot, Fallada...
It's true.
他们以前造访过地球
They visited Earth before.
- 另一个男的怎么样了？
- 还没找到
What about
the other male, Fallada?
He's free.
- 你有那个女孩？
- 是的
You have the girl?
- 我们很快就会到那里，稍等
- 我会等的
Yes.
We'll be with you
as soon as we can, hold on.
We'll try.
- 当你说话的时候，这个来了
- 是什么？
This came through
while you were talking, sir.
总理发给珀西爵士的密电
- What is it?
- A scrambled cryptogram.
It's to Sir Percy
from the Prime Minister.
我们将直接到白宫的根据地
We're to proceed directly
to the Citadel at Whitehall.
Came--
中尉，控制住！
Lieutenant, the controls!
我们已失去她了，她走了！
We've lost her. she's gone.
- 到哪里去了？
- 她的身体在伦敦
Where?
Her body's in London.
伦敦的哪里？
Where in London?
what really happened
on the Churchill.
不是罗林斯毁坏了无线电设备…
It wasn't Rawlings who destroyed
the radio equipment.
和飞船的磁带
And the ship's tapes.
- 是我
- 为什么？
It was me.
我不想邱吉尔号回到地球
Why?
I didn't want the Churchill
to be able to reach Earth.
如果回来了，我不想要任何人知道发生了什么
And if it did, I didn't want anyone
to know what happened.
发生什么？
What did happen?
我打开了密封好的盒子
I opened her sealed
animation case.
不知道是我还是她打开的
Either I did it or she did it.
我无法控制自己
I couldn't help myself.
我从没有如此经历
I've never experienced such--
我坠入了爱河，你不知道的，肯
I was in love on a level
you've never known, Caine.
那使我害怕
It terrifies me.
我的命运和我开了玩笑
My memory plays tricks on me.
她在呼唤我
She was calling me.
她的力量是精神上的
Her power was...spiritual.
肯，她想要我
She wanted me, Caine.
比精神力更强
It was more than spiritual.
她拿走了我的一些生命能量
She took some of my energy.
并给了我一些她的能量
And she gave me
some of her energy.
当我们发现他们之前，
他们应该是彼此倚赖着生活
They must have been living off
of each other when we found them.
他们只有三个留了下来
There were only three
of them left.
她杀了我们的人，一个接一个
She killed all of my men.
One by one.
只有我幸存
But I survived.
她想要我留下来，她选择了我！
She wanted me to survive.
She chose me!
为什么？为什么？
Why, why!
她不是人类，她不是一个女人
Carlsen, she's not human,
she's not a woman.
她会毁掉你
She'll destroy you.
她会毁掉整个世界
She's destroyed worlds.
有些事你应该想听，长官
There's something
you might want to hear, sir.
英国广播公司的特别报道
A special bulletin
from the BBC.
今晚，伦敦在毁灭的边缘…
It's obvious that tonight,
自从闪击战以来，最严重的灾难
London is on the brink of the worst
devastation since the blitz.
城市的大片区域在燃烧，完全不受控制
From where I'm standing,
I can see large areas of the city
burning out of control.
成千上万的人正慌乱地经过街道
在混乱中，尽可能地逃难
And thousands of people are now
rampaging through the streets here
in a frenzied last effort
to avoid the plague.
已经实施戒严三个多小时
Martial law has been enforced now
for three hours
但显然无法阻止
But for the moment,
it hasn't stemmed what is obviously...
- 我们一直在等你
- 谢谢，继续坚持
Yes, sir, we've been
expecting you.
- 快点过去，警官
- 好的，长官
Thank you, carry on.
- Carry on, Sergeant.
- Right, sir.
- 到那一边去
- 好的
- Hilggins, around the other side.
- nght.
已准备疏散内阁吗？
ls everything ready
for the cabinet to evacuate?
- 准备好了
- 请坐，先生
Yes, everything.
Please take e seat. gentlemen.
长官，肯上校及卡尔森上校在等你
Sir, I have Colonel Caine
and Colonel Carlsen here for you, sir.
很好
Very good.
总理不久就会接见你
等的时候要喝杯茶吗？
The Prime Minister
will see you shortly.
Uh, would you care for a cup of tea,
while you wait?
- 不要了，事情很紧急
- 总理已经知道
No, our business is
rather urgent.
Yes, I'm sure the Prime Minister
understands that.
- 先生
- 总理
- Oh, uh, gentlemen?
- Prime Minister.
我是空军勤务处肯上校…
I'm Colonel Caine,
Special Air Service,
我相信你已经听到过邱吉尔号的卡尔森上校
and I'm sure you've heard of
Colonel Carlsen, late of the Churchill.
顺便问一下，珀西爵士在哪里？
By the way, uh,
where is Sir Percy?
恐怕已经去世了
Dead, I'm afraid.
哦，那非常遗憾
Oh, that's a great pity.
长官，我们有关于天空中那个物体的消息
Sir, we have information regarding
the object in space,
- 是那个正在冲向地球的…
- 是的，先生
which is bearing down on the Earth
at this moment--
Ye-ye-yes, gentlemen, look, if you'll
excuse me just-- just for a moment.
抱歉，请等一会
哈弗沙姆小姐，到这里来
Mi-- Miss Haversham,
please come this way.
好的，等一会
Miss Haversham, here,
for a moment.
我马上回来，先生
I'll be back, gentlemen,
I'll be back.
Miss Haversham,
come this way.
请
Miss Haversham, please.
马上叫医生来
Mind his head.
Go and get
the doctor immediately.
Hey, what's happening
down there?
我们这里需要一个医生
Need a doctor over here.
走！
Go, go!
- 飞机上有武器吗？
- 没有，长官！
Lieutenant, do you have
any weapons aboard the craft?
- 有一把闪光手枪
- 在哪里？
No, sir, uh,
there's a flare pistol, sir.
缺口旁边，已经上膛了
Where is it?
Just close the breach
and it's ready to fire.
抓住他！
当你和总理在一起时，
我接到空军基地的电话
Sir, while you were with the PM,
I had a call from base operations.
城市已经戒严，我们由北约指挥
The city is now
under martial law.
We've been placed
under NATO command.
在S.R.C. 着陆，我们必须和法拉达谈谈
My unit's been mobilized
across the river
to a staging area
at Blackheath.
Land at the S.R.C., Lieutenant,
we've got to talk to Fallada.
我们在布莱克希思着陆，空军已封锁整个城市
I've been ordered to land
at Blackheath, sir.
The city's now
under air quarantine.
如果不按命行事，我们会被他们击落
If we don't do as they say,
they'll shoot us out of the air.
零号，我是X射线318号，
请求清除障碍，请求着陆，完毕
Hello, zero, this is x-ray 3-1-8
requesting clearance to land-- over.
我是零号，知道了，
X射线318号，你们可以着陆
Zero roger, x-ray 3-1-8,
you are clear to land.
离开飞机！你们在封锁区！
Come away from the aircraft.
You are under quarantine.
到这里来，长官
Over here, please, sir.
不要过来！站在那里！
Don't come any closer,
stop there!
我想和你们的指挥官谈谈
I want to talk
to your commanding officer.
我是空军勤务处肯上校…
I am Colonel Caine,
Special Air Service.
他是汤姆·卡尔森上校
And this man
is Colonel Tom Carlsen,
美国空军邱吉尔号前指挥官
United States Air Force and former
commander of the Churchill.
c company, be on stand-by.
S.R.C.的汉斯·法拉达博士在这里吗？
Is Dr. Hans Fallada here
from the S.R.C.?
- 他知道我们是谁
- 不，我不知道
He knows who we are
and what's going on.
No, not that I know of.
- 有人听说过他吗？
- 没有
- Has anybody heard of him?
- No.
他一定还在伦敦
Must still be in London.
上校，你一定知道那里发生什么事了？
Colonel, what exactly do you know
about what's happening over there?
我们确实知道，
那里发生了一场横扫伦敦的灾难
All we know
for certain, Colonel,
is that a terrible plague
of some sort is sweeping London.
潜伏期好像是二小时
The incubation period
appears to be two hours.
到那时为止，我不能让你们通行
And until that time
has elapsed,
I cannot release you
from this compound.
我们知道瘟疫是什么，我们没有感染
Colonel, we know
what the plague is.
我知道我们在讨论什么！简直在浪费时间！
We are not infected.
I know what I'm talking about
and we're wasting valuable time.
我们已经完全把伦敦隔离
为了阻止进一步的传染
We have totally isolated London
in order to stop further contagion.
如果失败了，将会威胁到周围的地区
If that fails and the surrounding
areas are threatened,
是的
Yes?
已获准使用核武器
Sterilization by thermonuclear device
has been approved.
我们有布鲁塞尔·埃姆斯上将的授权
We have this
from General Ames in Brussels.
他将在三小时内做出决定
He's coming up
with that decision in...
Just under three hours.
你知道与飞船有关的事吗？
Have you heard anything
about the ship?
- 太空飞船？
- 从哈雷慧星来的？
Corporal Adams...
- The ship?
- The thing from Halley's Comet.
Oh...
它停在伦敦上空的地球轨道上
It's parked itself
in a geostationary orbit...
Directly over London.
Would air adjutant report
to Major Grover in GHQ.
那些穿过云层的蓝色光茫像是人类的灵魂
All those little blue lights going up
toward the clouds,
they're human souls.
- 你怎么知道的？
- 我感觉得到
How do you know that?
I feel it.
他们可以将别人释放的生命能量
收集后转变为自己的
The process of conversion
releases a life energy.
“收集”？
Then it can be collected.
Collected?
那个伞状的家伙是个搜藏家？
Is that what the umbrella is?
能源不由自主地就到那里去了
Collector?
The energy doesn't go free.
It goes up there.
那个男吸血鬼正在收集生命能量
The male vampire's
collecting life energy.
但必须通过那女的送到伞状物那里
But he has to send it through her
to get it up to the collector.
她在哪里？
Where is she, Carlsen?
就在那边
Over there.
她的身体在发光
I get flashes coming
from her body.
她在收集能量时能够感知环境
Sensitive to its environment.
Picks up things.
- 你可以找到她吗？
- 如果我能够穿过这座城市
I” can get across to the city.
Can you find her?
He'll come
if he senses I've found her.
- 她在拉我
- 卡尔森！
She's drawing me, Caine.
Caflsen.
我必须到那里去
I've gotta go.
为什么？
Why?
她想把给我的能量拿回去
She wants back
the energy she gave me.
当他们具有新的生命形式时…
When they take on
a new life form
他们必须从那种生命形式学习
they have to learn
from that life form.
在某种意义上说，是适应新的生命形式
Mate with it, in a sense.
那女孩选择了我
The girl chose me.
当她与我结合时，她把她的一部分给了我
But when she mixed with me,
she gave me a part of herself.
现在她想把那部分拿回去
And now she wants
that part back.
在你那个地区有什么活动的迹象吗？完毕
Is there any sign of activity
in your sector?
- 没有，长官
- 好，保持联系，完毕
- Over.
- No, sir.
Okay, keep me posted-- over.
上校，听我说，
卡尔森上校说他能找到那个女的的位置
Colonel, listen to me.
Carlsen believes
he can locate the source.
If we can destroy them, it may not
be necessary to destroy London.
但我们只有一个半小时了
But we only have
an hour and a half.
What was that?
停火！
Cease firing!
卡尔森！
Caflson?
He knocked over two of my men
and took an armored Land Rover.
He wanted to know where
the Space Research Center was?
罗杰告诉了他，然后我就倒在了地上
Rogers told him, the next thing I knew,
I was on the ground, sir.
- 好，这是谁的汽车？
- 那辆？
Right, whose is this car?
- 那是上校的
- 给我钥匙
- That, that's the Colonel's, sir.
- Give me the keys.
- 什么？
- 我要征用这辆车！
- What?
- You heard me.
Give me the bloody keys,
I'm commandeering the car!
把钥匙给他
Give it to him.
还有你手上的家伙
And your side arm.
你真的知道你在做什么？
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
如果你进去了，我不会允许你出来
You realize once you're inside there,
we can't allow you out.
- 小心！
- 他过来了！
Where is he going?
肯上校，S.A.S.，我们要过河
Colonel Caine, S.A.S.,
I'm crossing the river.
- 你不要到那里去
- 我知道不可以的
You don't want to go
in there, sir.
I know I don't.
到大门的适当位置！保护这个部位！快！
Get them gates
in position!
Secure this post-- move!
卡尔森，卡尔森
Carlsen, Carlsen.
卡尔森
Caflsen.
Carlsen.
卡尔森，卡尔森
Car/sen.
- 法拉达
- 肯
FaHada?
很高兴见到你还没死
Caine.
I'm glad to see you alive.
我会报答你的
I reciprocate the sentiment.
- 这次他真的死了？
- 这是杀死他们的唯一办法
Is he really dead?
This time?
The only way
they can be killed.
- 柯斯基在哪里？
- 死了
Where's Bukovsky?
Dead.
- 怎么死的？
- 像其他人
How?
Like the rest.
你怎么没死？
How did you survive?
- 你正找卡尔森上校吗？
- 他在这里吗？
You're looking for Carlsen.
多半是编号误导了你
Has he been here?
No, perhaps he misled you.
- 关于他们（吸血鬼），你知道多少？
- 我已经做了很多工作
What do you know about it?
I've been doing some more work.
- 继续
- 我已经发现…
Go on.
I discovered
死后的灵魂
there is life after death.
- 你怎么知道的？
- 有某种办法可以进行精神转换
How do you know?
在吸血鬼和受害人之间发生了心灵感应
There is a certain
mental transference, telepathy,
that occurs between the vampires
and their victims.
- 卡尔森上校是那女孩之后的
- 你是如何知道那些的？
Carlsen is after the girl.
How did you know that?
Oh, I...
- 我似乎感觉到她
- 她在哪里，法拉达？
I seem to sense it.
Where is she, Fallada?
你不知道吗？
Don't you know?
- 卡尔森上校知道
- 在哪里，法拉达？
Carlsen knows.
Where, Fallada?
她在教堂里
She's in the cathedral.
她逃脱后就一直在那里
She's been there
since she escaped.
与她接触的感觉相当好，你不想吗？
Rather a nice touch,
don't you think?
国王和皇后的地窖
The crypt of kings
and queens.
站在那里
Stay where you are.
Stay where you are!
我到那里去
Here I go.
我知道你会来，卡尔森
I know you would come,
Carlson.
Now can this madness end?
过来
Come.
与我在一起
Be with me.
我需要你
I need you.
我一直计划
It was always intended
你们应该可以找到我们…
并带我们到地球
you should find us
and bring us to Earth.
命运之网带着你的灵和肉…
The web of destiny carries
your blood and soul
回到我的生命本源
back to the genesis
of my life form.
过来，你和我…
Come.
Be with me.
跟我来，卡尔森
Come with me, Carlsen.
如果你到我这里来，就会不再害怕…
It'll be much less terrifying
if you just come to me.
我只想这样做
I'll do just that.
Cansen!
你感觉到吗？
What are these feelings?
为什么我觉得如此亲近你，如此需要你？
Why do I feel so close to you?
因为你是我们中的一个，你一直都是
Need you?
Because you're one of us.
You always have been.
你喜欢我，喜欢和我在一起
You're like me.
Be with me.
只有这些？只有这些？
Just a little more.
卡尔森！
Cansen!
Carlsen!
卡尔森！
肯！
Caine!